(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T22:16:41.415279",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary LIVE
常闇トワ 6周年記念 Live Rock Festa!!!
Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary Live Rock Festa!!!
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
輪堂千速
Rindo Chihaya
IRyS
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
AZKi
夏色まつり
Natsuiro Matsuri
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
猫汰つな
Nekota Tsuna
あぁ 呆れ出す粗暴に差し替えられた
Ah, replaced by a disgusted roughness,
現存に掛かった固定解答
a fixed answer stuck on existing reality.
反則じみた応えじゃ見透かされてしまうな
A cheat-like response will only be seen right through.
この道を渡り切っても まだ視界は曇っている
Even if I cross this road, my vision is still clouded.
履き替えた大人になってから縮み切った歩幅と感情
Since becoming an adult with new shoes, my stride and emotions have shrunk.
削り出した身体に対して「気付け」と歌ってる
I sing "wake up" to my worn-down body.
はみ出した心じゃ居られないのならさ
If I can't stay with a heart that overflows,
染み付いたこの青さを切り離してしまっていい？
is it fine if I detach this ingrained youthfulness?
ずっと語りかけてた日々を嘆くように
As if grieving the days I kept speaking to,
「深い闇に呑み込まれないように」って
saying, "Don't let the deep darkness swallow you whole."
染まり切った現実にと答えなんてない
There is no answer in a fully painted reality.
逃げ出してしまった言葉を羽織って
Cloaking myself in words that ran away,
溶け出した心を胸に隠している
I hide my melting heart inside my chest.
冷え切ってしまった身体を騙すように
As if deceiving my completely chilled body,
描きかけたいつかの枯れたい夢をなぞっている
I trace over a withered dream I once began to sketch.
あぁ 暴れ出す言葉に差し替えられた
Ah, replaced by words bursting out,
幻想に掛かった固定概念と
with fixed concepts caught in an illusion
止まった理想じゃ見透かされてしまうな
and a stalled ideal, I'll surely be seen through.
この道を渡り切っても また次回だ続いていく
Even if I cross this road, it continues onto the next.
履き違えた大人になってから尖りだした思いの回想
Recollections of feelings sharpened after becoming a mistaken adult.
ずっと見えなくなった足跡探している
I keep searching for footprints that disappeared long ago.
はみ出した心じゃ居られないのならさ
If I can't stay with a heart that overflows,
澄み切ったこの青さを曝け出してしまっていい？
is it fine if I expose this crystal-clear youthfulness?
ずっと語りかけてたヒビを隠すように
As if concealing the cracks I kept speaking to,
「深い闇に呑み込まれないように」って
saying, "Don't let the deep darkness swallow you whole."
決まり切った現実にと答えなんていらない
I don't need answers in a predetermined reality.
逃げ出してしまった言葉を羽織って
Cloaking myself in words that ran away,
溶け出した心を胸に隠している
I hide my melting heart inside my chest.
冷え切ってしまった身体を騙すように
As if deceiving my completely chilled body,
描きかけたいつかの枯れたい夢をなぞっている
I trace over a withered dream I once began to sketch.
あぁ 錆び付いている
Ah, rusting away,
今をただ不安定に立つ
I merely stand unstably in the present.
裏返る脳裏に汚されてしまったあの日常
That daily life tainted in my flipped consciousness,
願っては辿ってた手放してしまったのに
even though I wished, traced, and ultimately let go of it.
逃げ出してしまった言葉を羽織って
Cloaking myself in words that ran away,
溶け出した心を胸に隠している
I hide my melting heart inside my chest.
冷え切ってしまった身体を騙すように
As if deceiving my completely chilled body,
描きかけたいつかの枯れたい夢をなぞっている
I trace over a withered dream I once began to sketch.
Can you hear me when I cry in desperation?
Nothing comes along with my expectation
How much pain and ache you're feeling?
Breathing...
I gotta change this situation
アダルトなキグルミ着てる僕
Wearing an adult kigurumi, I'm...
ここはいつも不安定 天秤シーソー
My heart is always unstable, a seesaw balance
まさかの発言で凍り付かす
Freezing everything with an unexpected remark,
印籠見え隠れ
an inro appears and disappears,
血迷うボク
and I'm losing my mind.
今日の今この瞬間に放とうとする
The words I try to release into today's, this very moment,
言葉がいつも後ろ髪引く
always pull me back.
全部ダメダメ なんでしょ？ じゃあもう放棄して！
Everything is no good, right? Then just abandon it!
ハナから無かった事にしよう！！
Let's pretend it never happened from the start!!
ラリルラリルラ
Rari-ru rari rari-ra
それじゃダメダメ 悪い癖だね もうしない！
That's no good, it's a bad habit! I won't do it anymore!
どうせ着せられているなら
Anyway, if I'm being dressed in this,
キメキメでいこう！
let's go with a decisive style!
何もかもが暗く黒く見える！
Everything looks dark and black!
色メガネ付きの
With tinted glasses,
アダルトなパチモンスーツ
an adult cheap-knockoff suit.
必殺技×0で全部
Shall I erase everything
消し去ろうか？
with finishing move x 0?
強気なボク（笑）
A confident me (lol)
だけど実際はやっぱ出来やしないの
But actually, after all, I can't do it,
身軽さを奪われ動けない
robbed of my agility, I can't move.
それで上手いことバランスとれてるんだよ！
And yet, you balance it out skillfully!
君は耳元でそれを言う！
You whisper that right in my ear!
それにしちゃ少し
Isn't that a bit too much?
あんまりじゃない？ っていうか不公平じゃない？
Or rather, isn't it unfair?
どうせ勝ち目なんてないし
There's no chance of winning anyway,
食い気味でいこう！
so let's charge ahead eagerly!
I feel this moment
No one can take it
そう何回だって伝わらなけりゃ意味無い！
Yes, no matter how many times, if it doesn't get across, it's meaningless!
今日の今この瞬間が大事なの！
Today's, this very moment is what matters!
奪う権利はあなた方にはない！！
You don't have the right to take it away!!
全部ダメダメ！ 何がダメダメ？ なんでしょう？
Everything is no good! What's no good? Why is it?
納得いくまで話してよ！
Talk to me until you're satisfied!
どうせ屁理屈並べるんだろ？ バカみたい
You're just going to make up sophistry anyway? How foolish.
とどめを刺す気でいるなら？
If you're planning to deliver the finishing blow?
今がチャンスだぞ！
Now is your chance!
はーい！
Hi~!
ということで、ホロライブ4期生の常闇トワ様でーす！
And so, I'm Tokoyami Towa-sama from Hololive 4th Generation!
はい、ということで、なんと本日6周年を迎えました！
Yes! So, today I'm actually celebrating my 6th anniversary!
イエーイ！
Yay!
6！ 6！
6! 6!
悪魔の数字 6！
The devil's number, 6!
ということは、今年はトワちゃんの年ということで、もういいでしょうか？
Which means, is it okay to say that this year is Towa-chan's year?
ま、よくないか！
Well, maybe not!
いいか！
Or maybe it is!
ま、人によってはトワちゃんの、ね、あの年にしたっていいということで。
Well, depending on the person, it's fine to consider it Towa-chan's year.
はい、よろしくお願いします！
So yes, thank you very much!
こんやっぴー！
Kon-yappi~!
ててててて...
Te-te-te-te-te...
えー、常闇トワ6周年記念ライブでよろしくお願いします！
Welcome to Tokoyami Towa's 6th Anniversary Live!
目指せトレンド入り！
Let's get this trending!
えー、そしてね
And also...
えー、この後はね、いろんな告知もありますので、最後まで見ていってくれればなと思います！
we have various announcements coming up, so I hope you stick around until the end!
はい！
Alright!
えー、で、今日なんですけれども、
Now, as for today...
えー、1月3日となっておりまして、
it's January 3rd,
えー、世間はお休みの日ということで、
and since it's a holiday for everyone,
えー、私もお休みの日ということで
and a holiday for me as well...
本日のライブは全編収録となっております！よろしくお願いいたします！
today's live concert is fully pre-recorded! Please enjoy!
そして！
And...
えー、この後はなんと、ゲストパート！
right after this is the guest section!
いっぱい色んなね、ゲストが出てきてくれるので、楽しんで見ていってくれればなと思います！
We have lots of wonderful guests coming on, so please enjoy watching!
では！ゲストパート、どうぞ！
Now then, please enjoy the guest section!
絆ノ奇跡
[Song: Kizuna no Kiseki]
闇夜を駆け抜けて どこへ向かう
Running through the dark night, where are we heading?
月明かりだけが ただ一つの道標
The moonlight alone is our only signpost.
痛みも悲しみも 拭いきれず
Unable to fully erase the pain and sadness,
されどこの胸の 炎は消させない
yet I won't let the flame in this chest be extinguished.
誰が為に僕たちは この想いを貫いて
For whose sake do we carry out these feelings,
闇夜を裂き 陽の下で 光さす日まで
tearing through the dark night under the sun, until the light shines?
解き放たれた 心に宿した火よ
O unleashed fire that dwells within our hearts,
舞い上げ 纏え 今 夜明けの向こう側へ
soar high and wrap around us, now toward the other side of dawn!
君がいる この世界 もう一度愛せるまで
Until I can love this world where you exist once more,
我が命 果てようとも 繋いで行こう
even if my life comes to an end, let's keep connecting.
絆が紡いで 生まれた奇跡を
To the miracle born, spun from our bonds.
喜怒哀楽 夢 揺らめいてる現世
Joy, anger, sorrow, pleasure—dreams flickering in this transient world.
互いの正義を また繰り返し振りかざす
Wielding our mutual sense of justice once again.
誰が為に繋ぐ命 混ざり縺れる運命
For whose sake do we connect our lives? Destinies intertwining and tangling.
蛇の道 数多の罪 全て薙ぎ払え
The snake's path, countless sins—mow them all down!
解き放て 今 僕らが起こした火を
Release it now, the fire we have ignited!
舞い上げ 走れば 明日が変わるはず
Soar high, if we run, tomorrow is bound to change.
君といる この世界 二度と離さずに
In this world with you, never letting go again,
君と共に行く
I will go together with you.
瞼を閉じていても 思い出すあの日を
Even with my eyes closed, I remember that day.
打ちのめされても 焦がれた未来を
Even if knocked down, I long for the future.
いつの日か君に 捧げてみせよう
Someday, I will dedicate it to you.
解き放たれた 心に宿した火よ
O unleashed fire that dwells within our hearts,
舞い上げ 纏え 今 夜明けの向こう側へ
soar high and wrap around us, now toward the other side of dawn!
解き放て 今 僕らが起こした火を
Release it now, the fire we have ignited!
舞い上げ 走れば 明日が変わるはず
Soar high, if we run, tomorrow is bound to change.
君がいた この世界 もう一度愛せるまで
Until I can love this world where you were once more,
我が命 果てようとも 繋げていくよ
even if my life comes to an end, I'll keep connecting.
絆が紡いで 生まれた奇跡を
To the miracle born, spun from our bonds.
抱きしめられた記憶から
From the memories of being held close,
流れ出た赤い雫
red drops flowed out.
人様に見せるものじゃないの
It's not something to show to others.
伝えなかった言霊が もうひとつの私になって
Unspoken words became another me,
身体の内側で何かを叫んでいる
shouting something inside my body.
欲しかったのに 悔しかったのに
Though I wanted it so badly, though I felt so much regret...
ダメだよ 全部品隠しておくの
No, you must hide it all away.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
悲しいのは一人で十分だからと
"Because sadness is enough for just one," you said,
これ以上醜くなりたくないのと
and "I don't want to become any uglier."
私の中で誰にも見つけられずに
Inside of me, unseen by anyone,
こんな色になるまで泣いていたんだね
you were crying until you turned this color, weren't you?
綺麗よ
You are beautiful.
渡しそびれた心から 流れ出た青い雫
From the heart I couldn't ever give, blue drops flowed out.
人様にかぶせるものじゃないの
It's not something to pour onto others.
余すことなく飲み込んで 遠くの海の底に沈んで
Swallowing it all down, sinking to the bottom of a distant sea,
そのまま宝石にでもなれるのを待つわ
I'll wait there, hoping to turn into a jewel.
本当は嘘で飾って
Decorating the truth with lies,
ごっこみたいな暮らしで慰めて
comforting myself with a life like make-believe,
誰かの悲劇で自分の悲劇を癒して
healing my own tragedy with someone else's pain,
恋しさに溺れた瞬間のままで
in that moment I drowned in yearning,
息も出来ずただ愛してるの
unable to even breathe, I just love you.
悲しいのは一人で十分だからと
"Because sadness is enough for just one," you said,
これ以上醜くなりたくないのと
and "I don't want to become any uglier."
私の中で誰にも見つけられずに
Inside of me, unseen by anyone,
こんな色になるまで泣いていたんだね
you were crying until you turned this color, weren't you?
綺麗よ
You are beautiful.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
ねぇ 綺麗よ
Hey... you are beautiful.
片っぽで丸を作って しっかり持ってて
Make a loop with one end, and hold it tight.
もう片っぽでその丸の後ろをぐるっと回って
With the other end, wrap around the back of that loop.
間にできたポッケに入って 出てくるの待ってて
Pass through the pocket created between, and wait for it to come out.
出てきたところを迎えに来て “せーの”で引っ張って
Catch it as it emerges, and pull together on "Ready, set..."
初めは何とも情けない形だとしても
Even if it looks somewhat clumsy at first,
同じだけ力をこめて
put equal strength into it.
羽根は大きく 結び目は硬く
Wings large, knot tight,
なるようにきつく結んでいてほしいの
I want you to tie it tightly so it stays.
手はここに 思い出は遠くに
Hands here, memories far away,
置いて おいて ほしい ほしいの
I want you to leave them... leave them there.
片っぽでも引っ張っちゃえば ほどけちゃうけど
If you pull on just one end, it will come undone,
作ったもの壊すのは 遥かに簡単だけど
though destroying something you've made is far easier.
だけどほどく時も そうちゃんと同じようにね
But even when untying it, do it just the same way.
分かってるよ でもできたらね 「せーの」で引っ張って
I know, but if you can, pull it on the count of "one, two."
ほどけやしないようにと 願って力込めては
Wishing it won't come undone, as I put strength into it,
広げすぎた羽に戸惑う
I'm bewildered by the wings I spread too wide.
羽根は大きく 結び目は強く
So that the wings are large and the knot is firm,
なるようにきつく 結んでいてほしいの
I want you to tie it tightly like that.
夢はここに 思い出は遠くに
Your dreams here and your memories far away,
気づけばそこにあるくらいがいい
it's good enough if they're right there when you notice.
黙って引っ張ったりしないでよ
Don't just pull silently,
結んだつもりがほどいていたり 緩めたつもりが締めていたり
thinking you tied it when you untied it, thinking you loosened it when you tightened it.
この蒼くて広い世界に 無数に散らばった中から
From among the countless threads scattered in this blue and wide world,
別々に出会った二人 選んだ糸を お互いたぐり寄せ合ったんだ
we each chose our own thread and pulled them closer to each other.
結ばれたんじゃない 結んだんだ 二人で「せーの」で引っ張ったんだ
We didn't just get tied, we tied it ourselves; the two of us pulled it on the count of "one, two."
大きくも小さくもなりすぎないように 力を込めたんだ
We put our strength into it so it wouldn't become too big or too small.
この蒼くて広い世界に 無数に散らばった中から
From among the countless threads scattered in this blue and wide world,
別々に出会った二人 選んだ糸を お互いたぐり寄せ合ったんだ
we each chose our own thread and pulled them closer to each other.
結ばれたんじゃない 結んだんだ 二人で「せーの」で引っ張ったんだ
We didn't just get tied, we tied it ourselves; the two of us pulled it on the count of "one, two."
大きくも小さくもなりすぎないように 力を込めたんだ
We put our strength into it so it wouldn't become too big or too small.
花になって
[Song: Become a Flower]
陰にそっと隠れようが良いんじゃない？
It's okay to quietly hide in the shadows, isn't it?
蕾のような花だってあるんじゃない？
Aren't there flowers like buds?
秘密にして守るのがいいんじゃない？
Isn't it good to keep it a secret and protect it?
誰にも邪魔されず華麗に咲いてる
Blooming brilliantly without being disturbed by anyone.
甘い苦いにハマんない
Not getting caught up in sweet or bitter,
その判断がくだんない
that judgment is worthless.
気に病んで下を向かないでいて
Don't look down worrying about it.
愛に慣れちゃいない
Not used to love,
無駄に飾らない
without unnecessary decoration.
綺麗にされた花瓶も
Neither a beautifully arranged vase,
肥やしも何もしらない
nor any fertilizer is needed.
その姿が美しい
That appearance is beautiful.
花になって
Become a flower,
ほらニヒルに笑って
hey, smile cynically.
その顔にぞくぞくして目が離せない
I can't take my eyes off your face, getting thrills from it.
味見して
Tasting it,
君の毒は私の薬って
your poison is my medicine.
笑って
Smile
逢いたい 逢いたい その笑顔に
I want to see, I want to see that smile
逢いたい 逢いたいって言えば笑ってくれるかな
If I say I want to see you, will you smile for me?
陰から支えるくらいはいいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine to just support you from the shadows?
欲を言えばこの手で咲かせてみたい
If I'm being greedy, I want to make you bloom with these hands
病のように
Like a disease,
心は喰らう花 枯らしたくないのさ
a flower eating away at the heart, I don't want it to wither
光が届かずとも
Even if the light doesn't reach,
水をあげ続けるから
I'll keep giving you water.
いい加減に気づいて 君は素敵って
Realize it already, that you're wonderful.
うぬぼれてもっとお大事に
Be conceited and take better care of yourself.
無自覚なまんま 愛を蓄えて
Store up love without even realizing it.
綺麗にされた花瓶も
A beautifully arranged vase,
肥やしも何もいらない
or fertilizer, you don't need any of it.
その姿で咲き誇れ
Bloom proudly just as you are.
花になって
Become a flower,
ほらニヒルに笑って
come on, smile nihilistically.
その顔にぞくぞくして目が離せない
I get thrills from that face and can't look away.
味見して
Take a taste,
君の毒は私の薬って
saying your poison is my medicine.
包んであげるから
I'll wrap you up,
楽にして
make yourself comfortable,
君の闇は私の光って
saying your darkness is my light.
愛してあげるから
I'll love you,
笑って
so smile.
ドライフラワー
[Dry Flower]
多分、私じゃなくて良くて
Maybe I wasn't the right one for you,
余裕のない二人だったし
we both lacked composure.
気付けば喧嘩ばっかりしてさ ごめんね
Before we knew it, we were always fighting, I'm sorry.
ずっと話そうと思ってた
I'd been thinking about talking to you for so long.
きっと私たち合わないね
We really aren't right for each other.
二人きりしかない部屋でさ
In that room with just the two of us,
あなたばかり話していたよね
you were always the one doing all the talking.
もしいつか何処かで逢えたら
If we ever run into each other somewhere,
今日の事を笑ってくれるかな
wonder if you'll be able to laugh about today.
理由もしっかり話せないけれど
Even though I can't really explain the reason well,
あなたが眠った後に脱ぐのは上着
taking off my jacket after you fall asleep.
声も顔も不器用なとこも
Your voice, your face, even your clumsiness,
全部全部 嫌いじゃないの
all of it, all of it, I don't hate.
ドライフラワーみたい
Like dried flowers,
君との日々も
our days together too,
きっときっときっときっと
surely, surely, surely, surely,
色褪せる
will fade away.
多分 君じゃなくてよかった
Maybe it's good it wasn't you,
もう泣かされることもないし
I won't be made to cry anymore.
「私ばかり」なんて言葉もなくなった
And phrases like 'It's always me' are gone now too.
あんなに悲しいお別れでも
Even after such a sad farewell,
時間がたてば忘れてく
as time passes, I start to forget.
新しい人と並ぶ君は
Standing beside someone new, I wonder,
ちゃんとうまくやれているのかな
are you doing well with them?
もう顔も見たくないからさ
I don't even want to see your face anymore,
変に連絡してこないでほしい
so please don't contact me out of nowhere.
都合がいいのは変わってないんだね
You being self-serving hasn't changed at all,
でも無視できずにまた少し返事
yet unable to ignore it, I reply a little again.
声も顔も不器用なとこも
Your voice, your face, even your clumsiness,
多分 今も 嫌いじゃないの
maybe even now, I don't hate them.
みたく
Like...
時間が経てば
As time passes,
きっと きっと きっと きっと
surely, surely, surely, surely,
色褪せる
they will fade.
月明かりには魔物が揺れる
Monsters sway in the moonlight.
きっと私もどうかしてる
I must be going crazy, too.
暗闇に色彩が浮かぶ
Colors float in the darkness.
赤黄藍色が胸の奥
Red, yellow, and blue deep inside my chest,
ずっとあなたの名前を呼ぶ
always calling out your name.
好きという気持ち また香る
The feeling of love scents the air once more.
声も顔も不器用なことも
Your voice, your face, even your clumsiness...
全部全部 大嫌いだよ
All of it, all of it, I hate so much.
まだ枯れない花を
These flowers that have yet to wither,
君に添えてさ
I offer them to you,
ずっと ずっと ずっと ずっと
forever, forever, forever, forever,
抱えてよ
hold on to them.
二人三脚 feat. 描汰つな
[Three-Legged Race feat. Nekota Tsuna]
「大丈夫」と
"I'm okay,"
また嘘をついた
I lied once again.
「無理しているの」
"You're overexerting yourself,"
声でわかるよ
I can tell by your voice.
バレているんだよ
I see right through you.
見ためだとか 性格だって 違うあなた
You, who are so different in looks and personality,
だけど似てる どこか意外とあって
yet we're surprisingly alike in some ways.
共鳴 すぐにしたんだ
We resonated right away,
惹かれ合った私たち
drawn to each other.
不思議なこの絆
This mysterious bond...
なんだか重ねられなくて
Somehow we couldn't align,
向き合い
facing each other,
目を語り合おう
let's speak with our eyes.
私がいね 頑張れる理由
The reason why I can do my best:
そう 一人じゃないから
Yes, because I'm not alone.
あなたが笑えば
When you smile,
私もつられる
I smile along with you.
隣合わせの心 連鎖してるよ
Our side-by-side hearts are linked together.
時には歩幅が ズレてしまうけど
Even if our strides get out of sync at times,
二人 呼吸を合わせ さあ 未来へ進んで行こう
breathing as one, let us move forward to the future.
どれくらいの順位かな 周りと比べて
I wonder where we rank, comparing ourselves to others.
果てしないトラック戦 追いつけるの？
Can we catch up in this endless track race?
なんて弱気な日も 激励し続けてくれた
Even on weak-hearted days, you kept encouraging me.
あなたにいつも感謝
I'm always grateful to you.
転んでも立ち上がる
Even if we fall, we get back up,
夢を叶えたいんだ
because we want to make our dream come true.
こんなにもね 打ち込めるのは
The reason I can dedicate myself like this is:
そう 仲間がいるから
Yes, because I have friends by my side.
あなたの悩みは 私が寄り添う
When you have worries, I'll stand by your side.
心が疲れたなら 休憩しよう
If your heart gets tired, let's take a rest.
遠慮はしないで そんな仲じゃない 二人
Don't hold back; that's not the kind of relationship we have.
肩を組んで ほら 何度でも乗り越え
Arm in arm, look, we can overcome anything time and again...
乗り越えるよ
...we'll overcome it all.
世界中が敵になっても
Even if the whole world becomes our enemy,
変わらずあなたの味方
I will always be on your side.
右と左
Right and left,
友達の私だよって 強く固く
"I'm your friend," tied strongly and tightly...
縛ったリボン
...like a ribbon bound together.
話題のドラマも
The trending dramas,
虹になってる空も
and the sky with a rainbow,
掴み取る栄光も
and the glory we grasp,
一緒に見たい
I want to see them all together with you.
あなたが笑えば 私も笑える
If you smile, I can smile too.
隣合わせの心 連鎖してるよ
Our side-by-side hearts are chained together.
いずれそれぞれの道を歩いても
Even if we eventually walk separate paths,
共に支え合おう さあ未来へと進んで行こう
let's support each other. Now, let's move forward into the future!
どこにいても二人三脚
Wherever we are, we're in a three-legged race.
with you...
できたー！できたー！
We did it! We did it!
2度目ですけど！
Even though it's our second time!
めっちゃ忘れてたからね！
Because we totally forgot it!
6周年！
6th Anniversary!
6...そっちで？
6... like that?
こっちじゃないの？こう？韓国はこうだよ。
Isn't it like this? Like this? In Korea, it's like this.
勉強になりました、ありがとうございます！
I learned something new, thank you!
6周年おめでとう！ありがとう！
Happy 6th Anniversary! Thank you!
嬉しい！そうなんですよ、実はこの前...
I'm so happy! So actually, the other day...
ルイのね、誕生日記念ライブに...
At Lui's birthday celebration live stream...
出させていただいたのね！
I was invited to perform!
今回ね！
This time, right!
なんかさ、初めてなんだよね！
You know, it was our first time!
そう、ホロライブのスタジオに来ました！
Yeah, coming to the Hololive studio!
めちゃくちゃ喜んで... イェーイ！
I was super excited... Yay!
すごい！えー、すごい！
Wow! Whoa, amazing!
イェーイ！ありがとう！わざわざ来てくれて！
Yay! Thank you! Thank you so much for coming!
いっぱい吸っていきます！
I'm gonna soak it all in!
初めてそう、ホロライブのスタジオで3Dでコラボしました！ありがとう！
That's right, it was our first time collaborating in 3D in the Hololive studio! Thank you!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
そして、なんと...
And on top of that...
2年ぶりですよ！
It's been two years!
そうなんだ！
That's right!
この『二人三脚』という曲をやらせていただいたんですけれど...
We performed this song "Futari Sankyaku", but...
トワの1stソロライブの時に...
back at Towa's 1st Solo Live...
初めてやって。振りを覚えてた？
was the first time we did it. Did you remember the choreography?
いや、もう...完全忘れてた！
No, I totally... completely forgot it!
でも分かる！色んなのやっていくとさ、忘れちゃうからね。しかも2年ぶりだし。
I get it! As you do so many different things, you forget. Plus it's been two years.
忘れちゃったけど... 前はシークレットゲストだったじゃん。
I forgot, but... last time you were a secret guest, right?
サムネで私がいる...
In the thumbnail, I was there...
あー！いるー！ってなって！
and everyone went "Ah! She's there!"
嬉しい！本当ね、あの曲...
So happy! Really, that song...
あそこで終わりじゃなくて、こうやってまた出来たのがすごく嬉しいので！
didn't end there, and being able to do it like this again makes me so happy!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ということでね、ソロライブの時にコラボして...
So, we collaborated at the solo live...
こうやって3Dでコラボすること無かったから...
but we never got to collaborate in 3D like this, so...
今日は皆さんに無料でお届けしているので！
since we're bringing this to everyone for free today...
無料です！
It's free!
じゃあ、写真タイムするか！
Well then, shall we do screenshot time?
する！
Let's do it!
改めて、どんなポーズが良いですか？
Once again, what pose would be good?
指を動かして...
Moving our fingers...
ダサい動き！
That lame motion!
陰キャピース！
Introvert peace sign!
可愛い！可愛くピースしてみてよ。
Cute! Try doing a cute peace sign.
何が可愛いの？これギャルピースじゃん！
What's cute? Isn't this the gal peace?
古いって言われない？大丈夫？
Won't people say it's outdated? Is it okay?
今の流行りは？
What's trendy right now?
今の流行り何？
What's the current trend?
これ？これ？
Is it this? Is it this?
えっ、同じのやってる！
Huh, you're doing the same thing!
私もやりたいです！
I want to do it too!
おーおーおー！
Oh, oh, oh!
ダサっ！
So uncool!
喜びのダンス！
Dance of joy!
あ、出た！アイドル！
Ah, there it is! Idol!
イェーイ！
Yay!
いっぱい撮ってねー！ありがとうー！
Take lots of screenshots, okay? Thank you!
可愛い！かっこいい！
So cute! So cool!
ツナちゃんも可愛いじゃないですか
Isn't Tsuna-chan super cute too?
えー、嬉しいです
Aww, I'm so happy.
なんか、はだけちゃってごめんなさいね
I'm sorry for showing so much skin!
トワちゃんにはないものを持ってる気がして、すごい
I feel like you have things Towa doesn't have, it's amazing!
やめてください
Please stop!
でも別に何とは言ってないんですけども
Though I didn't specify what!
あ、そう、そうでした
Ah, right, that's true.
はい、ということでね
Alright, so anyway...
今日は本当に来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming today!
こちらこそ！ありがとう！
Thank you as well! Thank you!
またコラボも…
Let's collab again...
しましょう！
Let me!
しよう！アソビ大全！
Let's! Clubhouse Games!
アソビ大全！
Clubhouse Games!
ということで、以上！
So with that, that's all!
猫汰つなでしたー！バイバーイ！
This was Nekota Tsuna! Bye-bye!
頑張ってー！
Do your best!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
第ゼロ感
[Dai Zero Kan]
群れを逸れて
Straying from the pack,
夢を喰わえた
holding onto a dream in my mouth,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like this would be the last time.
獣は砂を一握り撒いた
The beast scattered a handful of sand,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like this would be the last time.
不確かな夢叶えるのさ 約束の夜に
Fulfilling an uncertain dream on the night of promise.
微かな風に願うのさ 静寂の朝に
Wishing upon a faint wind in the quiet morning.
遠い星の証明は その腕に約束の飾り
Proof from a distant star, a token of promise on that arm.
まだ旅路の途中さ 幻惑の園に
Still in the middle of the journey, toward the garden of illusion.
霞んで消えた 轍の先へ
Beyond the tracks that faded into the mist,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like this would be the last time.
手負いの夢を紡ぎ直せば
If I reweave a wounded dream,
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like this would be the last time.
熱砂を蹴り抗うのさ 約束の前に
Kicking up hot sand and fighting back before the promise.
命綱は無いのさ サーカスの夜に
There's no safety net on the circus night.
まだ旅路の途中さ あの場所に加速するさらに
Still in the middle of the journey, accelerating even further toward that place.
雨上がりのシャンデリア 幻惑の園に
A chandelier after the rain, in the garden of illusion.
Swish da 着火 you
Swish da ignition you
迷走 smash dribble trapper kidding me now?
Straying smash, dribble trapper, kidding me now?
coyote steals the sound
coyote steals the pass
coyote steals the sound and pass
Swish da 着火 you
Swish da ignition you
pass code a penetrator ベース！bebop！ ゲット triple！buzz up ビート！
pass code a penetrator, bass! bebop! get triple! buzz up beat!
ワンラブ and mercy！ bebop！heat check！ vasco da gama ビート！
one love and mercy! bebop! heat check! vasco da gama beat!
pass code a penetrator ベース！bebop！ wanna buzz up ビート！ just wanna buzz up ビート！
pass code a penetrator, bass! bebop! wanna buzz up beat! just wanna buzz up beat!
脳内 更地 に extra pass クー アザ ドン イハビ
Extra pass in a vacant mind, coup hasard dans inhabile.
Swish da 着火 you
Swish, ignite it, you!
永遠の意味知らぬ君に
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
it is time to show the answer.
夢幻に続く
Continuing into fantasy,
螺旋の先へ
to the end of the spiral...
言い訳に聞こえた理由は
The reason it sounded like an excuse
儚い未来手繰った弱さ
was the weakness of tracing a fleeting future,
それを強さとはき違えている
mistaking that for strength.
憎い 憎い
Hateful, hateful,
醜い 醜い
hideous, hideous,
月を隠すほどの
enough to hide the moon,
黒く 黒く
black, black,
淀む心
a stagnant heart.
君さえいなければ
If only you weren't here...
ゆらいている ゆらいている
Swaying, swaying,
花のように意思をつなぐ
like a flower, connecting wills,
奪っていく 奪っていく
snatching away, snatching away,
嵐のように心を裂く
tearing hearts open like a storm.
永遠の意味知らぬ君に
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
it is time to show the answer.
夢幻に続く螺旋の先に
Beyond the spiral leading into fantasy,
待つのは誰
who is waiting there?
生まれ落ちた運命を飲んだ
Swallowing the fate I was born into,
背負った数の名前を覚えた
I remembered as many names as I bore,
爛れるほど心燃やす感情
emotions that burn my heart to festering.
憎い 憎い
Hateful, hateful,
醜い 醜い
hideous, hideous,
世界を分かつほどの
enough to divide the world,
怒り 怒り
anger, anger,
燃やす心
a burning heart.
君さえいなければ
If only you weren't here...
ゆらいている ゆらいている
Swaying, swaying,
花のように意思を繋ぐ
like a flower, connecting wills,
奪っていく 奪っていく
snatching away, snatching away,
嵐のように心を裂く
tearing hearts open like a storm.
永遠の意味知らぬ君に
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
it is time to show the answer.
夢幻に続く螺旋の先で
Beyond the spiral leading into fantasy...
鬼哭に耳を傾けた仕舞よ
Listening to the wailing of demons, it's over,
この身に宿る万物で終いよ
it ends with all creation residing in this body,
夢幻を他者に託した弱き人
a weak soul who entrusted fantasy to others.
命の輝きは幾星霜
The sparkle of life spans many years,
祈りの瞬きが照らす斜陽に
in the setting sun lit by a flickering prayer,
千夜を身に宿し
housing a thousand nights within,
解を押し付ける
imposing the solution.
枯らしていく 枯らしていく
Withering away, withering away,
夢幻の夜に花を裂く
tearing flowers open in a fantasy night,
繋いでいく 繋いでいく
connecting on, connecting on,
嵐に種を撒いていく
sowing seeds into the storm.
ゆらいている ゆらいている
Swaying, swaying,
花のように意思を繋ぐ
like a flower, connecting wills,
奪っていく 奪っていく
snatching away, snatching away,
嵐のように心を裂く
tearing hearts open like a storm.
永遠の意味知らぬ君に
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
it is time to show the answer.
夢幻に続く螺旋の先で
Beyond the spiral leading into fantasy,
待つのは誰
who is waiting there?
以上、ゲストパートでした！
That concludes the guest section!
ゲストパートでしたー！
That was the guest section! Yeah!
はい、ということでたくさんのメンバーがね お祝いしに来てくれました！やったー！
All right! So many members came to celebrate! Yay!
そして、本日の6周...
And now, for today's 6th anniversary...
ライブなんですけれども
As for this live concert...
ロックフェスみたいなのちょっとイメージしておめかしして
I envisioned a rock festival vibe and dressed up for it,
ちょっとね、ダンスよりも好きに動いてねのフリーの動きを多めにしてみたので
and rather than set dance moves, I included more free movement where we can move as we like,
それぞれのゲストとね、トワちゃんのね、個性がテーマのパフォーマンスになってるんじゃないかなと思います！
so I think it turned out to be a performance that really highlights everyone's individuality!
なので配信とかを見直して「えっ、ここ癖出てるな」とか思いながらもう一回改めて見ていただけると嬉しいです！
So I'd be happy if you rewatch the stream and notice all the unique quirks!
そして！まだこの後も歌いますからチャンネルはそのままで！
And! I'll still be singing after this, so stay tuned!
で、プチ告知させてもらいます！
Now, I'd like to make a quick announcement!
はい！
Yes!
セカンドソロライブで発表いたしました
As announced during my second solo live,
『勇者パーティーを追放された器用貧乏』というアニメの主題歌『シルベ』のMVが
the MV for "Shirube", the theme song for the anime "The Multi-Tool Hero Released from the Hero's Party",
この後配信が終わり次第、常闇トワチャンネルにて上がります！
will be uploaded to the Tokoyami Towa Channel right after this stream ends!
めちゃくちゃいいMVになったのでぜひぜひ見てください！
It turned out to be an amazing MV, so please check it out!
見ないと人生を損したとまではいかないかもしれないけど損するかもしれないぐらいです！
If you don't watch it, well, it won't ruin your life, but you'll definitely miss out!
はい！気合いを入れて作ってもらいました！
They put a lot of heart into creating it!
はい！よろしくお願いいたします！
Please look forward to it!
そしてアニメはなんと明日から放送開始！楽しみ！ぜひ見てね！
And the anime actually starts broadcasting tomorrow! Look forward to it! Make sure to watch!
そしてMVだけではありません！ありません！
And that's not all!
『シルベ』のなんとシングルCDが発売決定！
The single CD for "Shirube" has been confirmed for release!
本日から予約できます！
Pre-orders start today!
なんですけどこちらの詳細は配信の最後にまとめてお伝えするので、ここもチャンネルはそのままで！
However, I'll share all the details at the end of the stream, so stay tuned!
そしてさらに本日ね、周年記念なのでグッズのお知らせもあります！もちろん！
And what's more, since today is our anniversary, we also have merch announcements! Of course!
はい、こちらの詳細も後でまたお伝えしますので、チャンネルはそのままで！
Yes, I'll also share the details on that later, so stay tuned!
今日のキーワードは「チャンネルはそのままで」
Today's keyword is "stay tuned"!
えー、そしてね、メン限のミニライブも今日ありますので
Also, we have a members-only mini live stream today,
ぜひメンバーシップに入っていただけたら嬉しくて、チャンネルはそのままで！
so I'd be really happy if you joined the membership, and stay tuned!
どんだけ言うんだよって！
How many times am I gonna say that?!
はい、ということでありがとうございました！
Alright, thank you so much!
はい、じゃあ最後にね、一曲歌ってから告知しようかなと思うので、聴いてください！
Now then, I'm going to sing one last song before making the final announcements, so please listen!
最後の1曲、『シルベ』
The last song, "Shirube".
Watch out!!
Warning! Warning! 隣り合わせで
Warning! Warning! Side by side
May God bless you 言葉の綾ね
May God bless you, a figure of speech
Warning! Warning! 彷徨いながら
Warning! Warning! As I wander
I will stay true to myself 'cause of you
「はじめから」みたいに
As if starting from scratch,
何もない世界に
in a world where nothing exists,
理不尽に囚われる
trapped in absurdity,
黙ってしまうほどの恐怖はない。
there is no fear great enough to render me silent.
使い捨てるみたいに手を離したあなたに
To you, who let go of my hand as if throwing me away,
「昨日とはまるで違う」って
even if you realize "it's completely different from yesterday",
わかったところでしょうもない
it doesn't matter anymore.
変わっていく身体と心の中で響く voice
With my changing body and the voice echoing in my heart,
間違ってなかったと
believing I wasn't wrong,
ただこの空を眺めてる
I am simply gazing at this sky.
I still 重なってくたび
I still, every time things overlap,
思い出してしまうのに
even though I end up remembering,
誤魔化してしまうのは
is the reason I gloss over it
確かにあった後悔から？
because of the regret that truly existed?
誓ったはずなんだ
I was supposed to have sworn...
さよならすらシルベにしよう
Let's turn even goodbyes into a signpost.
光に触れるたび願ってしまうように
Just as I pray every time I touch the light,
And still I rise!!
染まっていく必要もない
There's no need to conform.
越えられない border
An impassable border,
揺れる意志を convert
convert this wavering will.
嘘で染めるような日々じゃ
In days painted with lies,
振り返ったときには heartache
when I look back, there's only heartache.
また夜が明ける wake up
Dawn breaks again, wake up,
夢の中の flavor
the flavor in a dream,
誰もいなくなった道を歩いている
I walk along a path where no one is left.
今の私に
Even hesitation weighs down on the me of today,
迷いすら重ねてくる
layering over me...
おとぎ話の正体
The true nature of fairy tales—
誤魔化しきれなかった
the heat in my heart that couldn't be concealed,
心が纏う熱を
longing illuminates it.
憧れが照らしてる
Longing illuminates it.
I still 重なってくたび
I still, every time things overlap,
思い出してしまうのに
even though I end up remembering,
誤魔化してしまうのは
is the reason I gloss over it
大人になった後悔から？
because of the regret of growing up?
月明かりの夜は さよならすら シルベにしよう
On a moonlight night, let's make even farewells our guide.
光を繋ぐたび 浮かぶ星座のように
Like a constellation emerging every time we connect the light,
選んできた道のりを今を いずれ後悔してしまう時が来ても
Even if a time comes when I regret the path I've chosen and where I am now,
私はまだ止まらない
I still won't stop.
夜空に浮かぶ月光を 見上げた空に散らばる
Looking up at the moonlight floating in the night sky, and the stars scattered across the sky,
星の宝石を
treating those starry gems...
道標にして 帰る場所
...as a guidepost to the place I return to.
I still 重なってくたび 思い出してしまうのに
I still end up remembering every time they overlap,
誤魔化してしまうのは 確かにあった後悔から？
Is the reason I try to brush it off because of the regrets that were definitely there?
誓ったはずなんだ さよならすら シルベにしよう
I was supposed to have sworn, let's make even farewells our guide.
光に触れるたび 願ってしまうように
Just as I find myself wishing every time I touch the light,
And still I rise!!
染まっていく 必要もない
There is no need to be dyed either.
どれも愛を模した true
Every single one of them is a true mimicking love.
はい！ということで常闇トワ6周年記念ライブを見ていただきましてありがとうございましたー！
Alright! Thank you so much for watching Tokoyami Towa's 6th Anniversary Live!
もうノンスープでお届けしてまいりましたが、いかがだったでしょうかー？
We brought this to you non-stop, but how was it?
たくさんね、えー、タグを使って感想コメントを待っておりまーす。
I'll be waiting for lots of your thoughts and comments using the hashtag!
ということで、えー、この後は、お知らせをさせていただきたいと思います！
So with that, I'd like to move on to some announcements!
まず1つ目！
First off, number one!
先ほどね歌った『シルベ』を収録したシングルの発売がー…決定しましたー！
The release of the single containing the song "Shirube" that I just sang... has been confirmed!
イェーイ！
Yay!
えー、今回のジャケット写真は、えー、Graph77さんに描き下ろしていただきましたー！
This time, the jacket artwork was specially drawn for us by Graph77!
えー、3月25日発売で、今回も全国流通での発売となります！
It will be released on March 25th, and once again it will be available nationwide!
イェーイ！
Yay!
えー、そしてね、なんと！カップリングには『Present Day』のライブバージョンが入ります！
And what's more, the coupling track will include the live version of "Present Day"!
えー、ユーアネつながりということでね、えー、『Present Day』はソロライブ、えー、常闇トワ 2nd Liveの音源を使用ーした、えー、楽曲が収録されておりますので、えー、楽しみにしておいてください！
Tying into the 2nd Live, the track uses audio from Tokoyami Towa's 2nd Solo Live, so please look forward to it!
はい！そして今回は、えー、完全生産限定盤と通常盤の2種をご用意しております。
Also, this time we have two editions available: the Complete Limited Edition and the Regular Edition.
ということで、こちら！ポン！
So here they are! Pow!
完全生産限定盤には、えー、オリジナルTシャツが入っております！今回の「シルベ」のジャケットイラストを使ったオリジナルTシャツとなっております。
The Complete Limited Edition includes an original T-shirt! It features the jacket illustration of "Shirube."
えー、通常盤には初回プレス限定特典としてジャケットイラストステッカーが入ってます！ステッカーもね、スマホに入れたり、えー、アケコンやパソコンとか、えー、に貼ってもらえたら嬉しいなと思っております！
The Regular Edition comes with a jacket illustration sticker as a first-press limited bonus! You can put it on your phone, arcade stick, PC, or wherever you like!
はい！
Alright!
えー、こちらは本日21時から予約開始なんですが、なんと！ホロライブ公式ECではこの配信中にCDが買えるようになってるかも！
Reservations for these start at 9:00 PM today, but guess what! On the official Hololive EC store, you might already be able to buy the CD during this stream!
ということで、えー、楽しみに待っててくだーさい！チェックしてねー！
So please look forward to it and check it out!
はい！
Alright!
そして2つ目なんですが、えー、常闇トワ活動6周年記念ライブグッズー！ライブじゃねえわ、えー、グッズー！
And second... Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary Live merch--! Not live, I mean merch--!
が発売いたします！イェーイ！
...is going on sale! Yay!
えー、今回は数量限定版もありますので、えー、ぜひチェックしてみてください！
We have a limited quantity edition this time too, so please be sure to check it out!
ということで、えー、気になる内容は…こちら！ポンと！
So here is a look at what's included! Boom!
えー、活動6周年記念フルセットこんな感じになっております！ジャジャン！では細かく見ていきましょう！
Here is the 6th Anniversary Commemorative Full Set! Ta-da! Now let's take a closer look!
まず1つ目はこちら！えー、「#Towavel してね！」アクリルジオラマスタンドー！ということでイラストは大熊まい先生に書いていただきました！
First up is this! The "#Towavel With Me!" acrylic diorama stand! The illustration was drawn by Mai Ookuma-sensei!
ちょっとね、大人っぽいトワちゃんと一緒に、あの、デート的なのを行ってもらえればなと思います。いつもねTowavelね、みんなしてくれててありがとうございます！
I hope you can go on a date-like outing with this slightly more mature Towa-chan. Thank you as always for all your #Towavel posts!
これね、あの、本体をね、こう取り出して、ま本体ってトワのことなんだけど、トワを取り出して、ね、一緒にね、写真が撮れるポージングにしてるので、ぜひ一緒にね、えー、Towavelしてポストしてみてねー！
The main figure—which is me, Towa—can be taken out, and the pose is designed so you can take photos together, so please go #Towaveling and post your photos!
はい、では次はこちら！
Alright, next up is this!
トワとお揃い！？ジャージ！えー、トワのね、通常衣装の、えー、服をイメージしたジャージとなっております。
Match with Towa!? Tracksuit! This tracksuit is modeled after my default outfit!
え、これね、あの、トワとまったく同じにすると、とんでもない露出、露出度になるので、えー、長めの…着やすい…
If it were identical to mine, it would reveal way too much skin, so it's made longer and easy to wear...
はい、着やすいね、サイズにさせていただいております。
Yes, we made it a size that's easy to wear.
良かった！
I'm so glad!
え、ちゃんと裏地もね、
And the lining inside, too,
えー、ネオンピンクみたいな形の
um, it's a neon pink type of...
ネオンピンク、形じゃないね、ネオンピンク色になってますから
neon pink—not shape, it's a neon pink color—
え、本当にトワ様を、え、になっちゃったみたいなジャージになってます。
so it's a track jacket that makes you feel like you've really become Towa-sama.
ちょっと大きめのサイズなんで、あの、みんな着やすいのかなと思います。
It's a bit oversized, so I think it'll be easy for everyone to wear.
はい。
Yes.
ということで、じゃあ最後3つ目！
So with that, here's the third and final item!
え、ビビハンドストラップ！
Um, the Bibi Hand Strap!
やっぱね、あの、結構あの、トワのジャージとかは結構あの、
You know, Towa's track jackets and stuff are pretty much...
ザ・グッズ、グッズというかさ、キャラグッズみたいな感じするんですけども、
like "the" character merch,
えー、通常使いもね、しやすいような
but I wanted something that's easy to use every day,
えー、使い勝手の良いようなグッズも欲しいなと思いまして、ハンドストラップを作ってみました！
and convenient, so I made a hand strap!
イエーイ！
Yay!
えー、カラーリングもね、すごい落ち着いていて、トワっぽい色になったんじゃないかなと思うので、ぜひ購入お願いいたします。
The color scheme is subtle and very Towa-like, so please check it out!
えー、こちら、えー、スマートフォンの画像ついておりますが、スマートフォンはついてきませんのでよろしくお願いいたします。
Um, a smartphone is shown in the image, but the smartphone is not included, so please keep that in mind.
よろしくお願いいたします。はい。
Thank you for understanding. Yes.
で、こちらのね、セットをご購入してくださった方には、
And for those who purchase this set,
えー、笑顔のトワの、えー、箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます！
you'll get a polaroid-style bromide card featuring a smiling Towa with a foil-stamped signature!
はい。
Yes.
で、そしてね、数量限定で直筆サイン入り、こちら直筆サインで、えー、お渡ししたいなと思っておりますので、ぜひどっちも手に入れてくれればなと思います。
And also, in limited quantities, there's a hand-signed version! I wanted to hand-sign these for you, so I hope you try to get both!
可愛い！よろしくお願いいたします。
Cute! Thank you so much.
ということで、えー、以上、こんな感じで、常闇トワ6周年記念のグッズの紹介でした！
And with that, that was the showcase for Tokoyami Towa's 6th Anniversary merchandise!
えー、シルベットね、常闇トワのグッズ両方よろしくお願いいたします！
Um, please check out both Silvett and Tokoyami Towa merchandise!
ということで、今日は見てくれてありがトワ！
So, thank you for watching today!
このあとはメン限でライブしますから、ぜひよろしくお願いいたします！
After this, I'll be doing a members-only stream, so please join in!
イエーイ！
Yay!
じゃあね！メンバーシップ加入と、え、グッズ購入と全部よろしくね！
Bye-bye! Please consider joining the membership and buying the merch!
あけおめ！バイバーイ！
Happy New Year! Bye-bye!